二零零七年，普通高等学校招生。
全国统一考试听力部分，该部分分为第一、第二两节。
注意，回答听力部分时，请先将答案标在试卷上。
听力部分结束前，你将有两分钟的时间将你的。答案转涂到答题卡上。
现在是听力试音时间。
试音到此结束，听力考试正式开始。
请看听力。
部分第一节，第一节，听下面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题，从题中
所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听完每段对话后。
你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题，
每段对话仅读一遍。
例如，现在你有五秒钟的时间看试卷上的例题。
你将听到以下内容。
你将有五秒钟的时间将正确答案标在试卷上。
趁。
山的价格为九磅十五便士，所以你选择
项，并将其标在试卷上。
现在你有五秒钟的时间阅读第一小题的有关内容
John, is Mark coming for tea tomorrow?
Yes, I told you yesterday Tracy.
Oh, did you?
Sorry, I must have forgotten.
What's the hurry?
We'd like you to stay for dinner.
Well, thank you, but Helen and I have to my parents at the railway station.
Hi Tom, we have to start the meeting without you.
I know, my flight was delayed because of the heavy rain.
But you are just in time for the discussion.
How much are these shoes?
Oh, they are $35 a pair.
Do you have size 9?
I'm afraid they are sold out.
5. Hi, I'm thinking of taking a trip during the Christmas holidays.
Where would you like to go?
Well, maybe somewhere
第一节到此结束。
第二节，听下面五段对话或独白。
每段对话或独白后有几个小题，
从题中所给的
三个选项中选出最佳选项。
听每段对话或独白前，你将有时间阅读各个小题。
每小。
题五秒钟。
听完后，各小题将给出五秒钟的作答时间。
每段对话或独白读两遍。
听下面一段对话，回答第六和第七两个小题。
现在。你有十秒钟的时间阅读这两个小题。
Jane, you are so young.
How can you sing so well?
Well, Mr. Green, I like singing very much.
And I've been doing this for a while.
Above all, I have Mr.
James as my teacher.
No wonder. I believe you'll do a wonderful job tonight.
Now, ladies and gentlemen, Jane Carter.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's welcome Jane Carter.
Jane, you are so young.
How can you sing so well?
Well, Mr. Green, I like singing very much.
And I've been doing this for a while.
Above all, I have Mr.
James as my Text 7.
听下面一段。
对话，回答第八至十小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Happy birthday, Jimmy.
Are you ready for the next present?
You mean there's more besides the watch?
Come with us.
It's in the car.
Now, here we are.
You've been talking about this for months.
Oh, it's a new computer.
It's just what I want.
I'm so happy about it.
Thank you so much, Mom and Dad.
Happy birthday, Jimmy.
Are you ready for the next present?
You mean there's more besides the watch?
Come with us.
It's in the car.
Now, here we are.
You've been talking about this for months.
Oh, it's a new computer.
It's just what I want.
I'm so happy about it.
Thank you so much, Mom and
听下面一段对话，回答第十一至十三小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Text 8. Excuse me, sir.
Can I help you?
My name is Jane Smith.
I'm a designer, looking for a job.
See my secretary?
She will set you up with the test.
When? Next month?
I can't wait that long.
Excuse me? I can't wait a month.
I need something sooner.
I'm sorry? Excuse me, sir.
Can I help you?
My name is Jane Smith.
I'm a designer, looking for a job.
See my secretary?
She will set you up with the test.
When? Next month?
I can't wait that long.
Excuse me? I can't wait a month.
I need something sooner.
I'm sorry? Text 9.
听下面一段对话，回答第十四至十七小题。
现在你有二十秒钟的时间阅读这四个小题。
Hi, Lily. How's your new flat?
It's great. I really like it.
How big is it?
It's one big room, but it has a bathroom and a small kitchen, too.
How far is it from the office?
It's only about ten minutes.
Ten minutes by bus or by car?
On foot. I walked to work this morning.
I was ten minutes early.
You are lucky.
I was ten minutes late.
What happened? All the buses came late.
What did Susan say?
She was late, too.
What happened to her?
She took the train and it was late, too.
Well then, you're really lucky after all.
But what are you going to do tomorrow?
I'll start out fifteen minutes earlier.
Hi, Lily. How's your new flat?
It's great. I really like it.
How big is it?
It's one big room, but it has a bathroom and a small kitchen, too.
How far is it from the office?
It's only about ten minutes.
Ten minutes by bus or by car?
On foot. I walked to work this morning.
I was ten minutes early.
You are lucky.
I was ten minutes late.
What happened? All the buses came late.
What did Susan say?
She was late, too.
What happened to her?
She took the train and it was late, too.
Well then, you're really lucky after all.
But what are you going to do tomorrow?
I'll start out fifteen minutes earlier.
听下面一段独白。
回答第十八至二十小题。
现在你有十五秒钟的时间阅读这三个小题。
Welcome to this class on English words.
I hope that all of you can hear me.
If not, please let me know.
I am Professor John Morris.
I'll be your teacher for the next thirteen weeks.
As you can probably tell, this is one of the most popular and crowded classes.
Indeed, every time these courses offered, this room is very full.
Why is that?
Well, in order to use the English language, it's very important to have at least a
basic understanding of how words are formed.
Just to one figure, and there are many.
There are about one million words in English.
If you are an English learner, you might wonder how you can possibly remember all of
these words. Well, for one thing, you don't have to.
No native speaker exists who knows all of the words in the English language.
Besides, there are shortcuts.
Shortcuts? Yes. For example, if you know how words are formed by using parts of
words from other languages, such as Greek and French, you'll understand a good
number of English words when you first come across them.
Let me put it this way.
Knowing the rules will help you master a large number of words.
This is probably the number one reason why this class is so popular.
Good afternoon, everybody, and welcome to this class on English words.
I hope that all of you can hear me.
If not, please let me know.
I am Professor John Morris.
I'll be your teacher for the next 13 weeks.
As you can probably tell, this is one of the most popular and crowded classes.
Indeed, every time these courses offered, this room is very full.
Why is that?
Well, in order to use the English language, it's very important to have at least a
basic understanding of how words are formed.
Just to one figure, and there are many.
There are about one million words in English.
If you are an English learner, you might wonder how you can possibly remember all of
these words. Well, for one thing, you don't have to.
No native speaker exists who knows all of the words in the English language.
Besides, there are shortcuts.
Shortcuts? Yes. For example, if you know how words are formed by using parts of
words from other languages, such as Greek and French, you'll understand a good
number of English words when you first come across them.
Let me put it this way.
Knowing the rules will help you master a large number of words.
This is probably the number one reason why this class is so popular.
第二节到此结束。
现在你有两分钟的时间，将试卷上的答案。
版图到客观题答题卡上。
听力部分到此结束。